We visited one of the mobile air defense
units guarding the Ukrainian capital
from attack by Russian drones.
Interceptor drones are responsible for
the majority of takedowns of Iranian
style shahids,
but they're not always the best option
as we found out.
The team launches a small quadcopter to
check for radio frequency signal
strength.
The plan is then to launch an
interceptor drone on a training
exercise.
But the screen goes blank and
communication with the drone is lost.
They suspect because of interference
launch.
Браунінг дійсно буде працювати. Це,
по-перше, дуже погана погода, яка
впливає на роботу операторов
перехоплювачих. Они не вилітають в дощ.
І повітряны ціли, які идут ниже
видимости радаров
до насотах до 100 м, також є цілями
мобільно-вогневих стрілецьких груп.
Поменякай.
Задавай, що за бляста?
>> А це глубоко шалонірована оборона, яка
включає різні віди озброєнь і засобів
ураження.
Сапсан. Сапсан, бам на зв'язку.
>> Ми завжди стараємося опановувати всі
новинки, які в нас є. Спочатку це були
звичайний впівдрований,
потім перехоплювачі.
І ми вважаємо, чим ми технологічні, тим
більше шансів у нас здобути перемог.
insider.com